[{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9248,"timeElapsed":55416},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":6138,"timeElapsed":61556},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4014,"timeElapsed":65573},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980357228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":8393,"timeElapsed":73968},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":9755,"timeElapsed":83729},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":7741,"timeElapsed":91471},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380207,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5474,"timeElapsed":96947},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":7175,"timeElapsed":104124},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5631,"timeElapsed":109757},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":13867,"timeElapsed":129206},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":20639,"timeElapsed":149846},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":7358,"timeElapsed":157206},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7651,"timeElapsed":164858},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":14935,"timeElapsed":179796},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":17453,"timeElapsed":197251},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":4392,"timeElapsed":201645},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7129,"timeElapsed":208776},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3932,"timeElapsed":212710},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6287,"timeElapsed":220630},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509124,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5233,"timeElapsed":225864},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7054,"timeElapsed":232921},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3165,"timeElapsed":236088},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7211,"timeElapsed":243301},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7568,"timeElapsed":250869},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5173,"timeElapsed":256043},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":3397,"timeElapsed":259442},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":7644,"timeElapsed":267088},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":9196,"timeElapsed":276286},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5126,"timeElapsed":282967},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3570,"timeElapsed":286538},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2943,"timeElapsed":289484},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3955,"timeElapsed":293443},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3159,"timeElapsed":296604},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4455,"timeElapsed":301061},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4073,"timeElapsed":305135},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6125,"timeElapsed":311262},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5645,"timeElapsed":316910},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":5139,"timeElapsed":323478},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3345,"timeElapsed":326825},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6011,"timeElapsed":332838},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3520,"timeElapsed":336360},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5625,"timeElapsed":341986},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980629334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4086,"timeElapsed":346074},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3881,"timeElapsed":349956},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":14364,"timeElapsed":364323},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7746,"timeElapsed":372071},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":14932,"timeElapsed":388661},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3852,"timeElapsed":392514},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980684091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":8315,"timeElapsed":400831},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4870,"timeElapsed":405703},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3762,"timeElapsed":409467},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6542,"timeElapsed":416011},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980706422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7149,"timeElapsed":423162},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5854,"timeElapsed":429018},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"143","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8478,"timeElapsed":437498},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":11977,"timeElapsed":451495},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":10152,"timeElapsed":461649},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4062,"timeElapsed":465713},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763206,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":14232,"timeElapsed":479946},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8451,"timeElapsed":488399},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980783602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":11941,"timeElapsed":500342},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980788469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4865,"timeElapsed":505209},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7936,"timeElapsed":513146},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7997,"timeElapsed":521146},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4358,"timeElapsed":525505},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980815832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5386,"timeElapsed":532571},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980820744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4911,"timeElapsed":537484},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4728,"timeElapsed":542213},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980830514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5039,"timeElapsed":547254},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4477,"timeElapsed":551733},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980839157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4163,"timeElapsed":555897},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4636,"timeElapsed":560535},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980853258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":9462,"timeElapsed":569998},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980857660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4399,"timeElapsed":574400},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6551,"timeElapsed":582426},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7424,"timeElapsed":589852},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980878456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5343,"timeElapsed":595196},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980891598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":13140,"timeElapsed":608338},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980895689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4088,"timeElapsed":612429},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980899159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3467,"timeElapsed":615899},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980906514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7353,"timeElapsed":623254},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980914049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7534,"timeElapsed":630789},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"131","question":"Do you find dancing embarrassing? Why or why not? Describe the last time you danced.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3958,"timeElapsed":634750},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980926940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4964,"timeElapsed":643680},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980930742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3801,"timeElapsed":647482},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3103,"timeElapsed":650586},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980938858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5008,"timeElapsed":655598},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980942786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3926,"timeElapsed":659526},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980951179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8391,"timeElapsed":667919},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980954622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3442,"timeElapsed":671362},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980958140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3516,"timeElapsed":674880},{"subjectID":"pzf1676oza","prolificID":"675aa6682c88b9ae292452ff","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2aaf1299ae928ee3318","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980961709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3567,"timeElapsed":678449}]